<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss>
    <channel>
        <title>Sample data for Learning Akka book study</title>
        <language>en-ca</language>
        <item>
            <title>Tarzan of the Apes</title>
            <guid>ebooks/78</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2016 05:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
            <author>Edgar Rice Burroughs</author>
            <link>http://localhost:9000/assets/ebooks/pg78.txt</link>
            <description>I had this story from one who had no business to tell it to me, or to any other. I may credit
                the seductive influence of an old vintage upon the narrator for the beginning of it, and my own
                skeptical incredulity during the days that followed for the balance of the strange tale.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>The Return Of Tarzan</title>
            <guid>ebooks/81</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2016 05:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
            <author>Edgar Rice Burroughs</author>
            <link>http://localhost:9000/assets/ebooks/pg81.txt</link>
            <description>"Magnifique!" ejaculated the Countess de Coude, beneath her breath.

                "Eh?" questioned the count, turning toward his young wife.  "What is it
                that is magnificent?" and the count bent his eyes in various directions
                in quest of the object of her admiration.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>The Beasts of Tarzan</title>
            <guid>ebooks/85</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2016 05:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
            <author>Edgar Rice Burroughs</author>
            <link>http://localhost:9000/assets/ebooks/pg85.txt</link>
            <description>"The entire affair is shrouded in mystery," said D'Arnot.  "I have it
                on the best of authority that neither the police nor the special agents
                of the general staff have the faintest conception of how it was
                accomplished.  All they know, all that anyone knows, is that Nikolas
                Rokoff has escaped."</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>The Son of Tarzan</title>
            <guid>ebooks/90</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2016 05:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
            <author>Edgar Rice Burroughs</author>
            <link>http://localhost:9000/assets/ebooks/pg90.txt</link>
            <description>The long boat of the Marjorie W. was floating down the broad Ugambi
                with ebb tide and current.  Her crew were lazily enjoying this respite
                from the arduous labor of rowing up stream.  Three miles below them lay
                the Marjorie W.  herself, quite ready to sail so soon as they should
                have clambered aboard and swung the long boat to its davits.  Presently
                the attention of every man was drawn from his dreaming or his gossiping
                to the northern bank of the river.  There, screaming at them in a
                cracked falsetto and with skinny arms outstretched, stood a strange
                apparition of a man.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Jungle Tales of Tarzan</title>
            <guid>ebooks/106</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2016 05:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
            <author>Edgar Rice Burroughs</author>
            <link>http://localhost:9000/assets/ebooks/pg106.txt</link>
            <description>TEEKA, STRETCHED AT luxurious ease in the shade of the tropical forest,
                presented, unquestionably, a most alluring picture of young, feminine
                loveliness.  Or at least so thought Tarzan of the Apes, who squatted
                upon a low-swinging branch in a near-by tree and looked down upon her.</description>
        </item>
    </channel>

</rss>
